The balls are wrapped
in a veil of my spiritual energy.
The balls glimmer gold,
about five centimeters in diameter.
You'll recognize it the instant you see it.
Nope, it's not anywhere.
That's impossible!
We'll never find anything that small!
If you searched this hard and you can't find it,
then someone probably took them already.
Huh?
The balls are filled
with a powerful life force.
Spirits and yokai monsters
are drawn to stuff like that.
They believe they'll come back to life
if they gather enough items with high life force.
That's why evil spirits attack people,
and try to steal life force from them.
Isn't that bad news?
If someone takes them,
there's no way to look for them.
Like I care about that.
- You're the one who lost them!
- Ow! Stop it.
You look for it with us, damn it!
You goddamn turds!
Oh, wait, hold on, that hurts, wait...
This treatment... I'll never forget it.
We should go home for now
and think of a different strategy.
Right.
Find them?
Not at all.
If you have no leads,
there's nothing you can do.
I'll ask people I know
if they have ball intel, too.
Ball intel?
Also, don't forget that you still have
Turbo Granny's powers inside you.
Seems it's not going haywire this time,
but it's still a dangerous power.
Stay put until you figure something out.
Okay!
Hey.
Are you going out with Ayase?
Huh? Oh, no, I'm not dating her.
Huh? Is that right? I see.
Then can you introduce us?
Ayase is super cute!
I've been wanting
to get to know her for a while now!
Miss Ayase is...
cute!?
I never even considered that.
I was just happy
that I made my first friend.
But wait, if I think about it,
she might be cute.
No, wait!
Miss Ayase is my friend!
Thinking she's cute is bad!
That's impure!
So you guys have, like, done it, right?
Huh?
Rumors say she'll sleep with anyone.
Huh? Who'd say such a thing?
Dunno. But it's true, right?
Come on, please...
Who is spreading those rumors?
Huh? What's going on here?
You wanna fight?
I asked you who was spreading
such rumors.
Ya see, Momo-chan...
ain't that kind of girl.
It's best not to spread rumors like that.
It's not me! I get it!
I get it, so let go of me!
Hey, what's up? You okay?
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
Calm down! Calm down!
Yo.
Looks like you're havin' a hard time.
I haven't been to a school in centuries.
It's gotten so nice.
What're you doing here of all places?
In the first place, aren't you quarantined
in Miss Ayase's house?
Seiko said, "Cat, you can roam free.
You can't do anything anyway."
I can see her saying that.
Anyway, aren't you in trouble?
That power is way too heavy
of a burden for you.
You should let me inside
your body once more.
Don't worry.
I'll leave as soon as
I regain my power.
It's a really simple process.
Give me a break!
You returning my balls
to me comes first!
I won't fall for slick talk like that!
Okarun!
Whatcha up to?
Miss Ayase! Actually, right now...
- Inside this is Tur—
- Shh! Quiet!
...bo Gra...
Ayase is super cute!
C-Cute...
What the hell?
Why are you shying away from me?
Um, well, it's not what you think.
Then look at me!
Um, hold on.
And like, stop!
Why are you running from me?
Wait, damn you!
It's not what you think!
- I'll kill your punk ass!
- Why!?
Guess I'll enjoy campus life
for the first time in a while.
Oof.
Momo, why you so mad?
What? Something happen with your bae?
For some reason he's totally avoiding me.
I'm seriously pissed.
And he ain't my boyfriend, either.
But he's a good guy.
Huh? That came from nowhere.
Whatcha talkin' about?
I heard from someone in Class C.
Okarun got in a fight with boys
who were badmouthing you.
What?
Seems someone is spreading
nasty rumors about you.
And I heard he got pissed about that.
Then why is he avoiding me?
I am just too pretty.
Everyone's eyes are glued to me
when I'm just walking down the hall.
And I'm not just cute.
I even greet the local blockheads
with a smile.
By believing that a pretty girl likes them,
they can live another day.
I am a pretty girl who is also kind.
But someone as perfect as myself
has things to get super upset about.
I wanted to get back at that bitch,
so I spread rumors that she's a slut.
But the rumor isn't spreading much.
So maddening!
They just don't get it at all.
She's a demon.
I saw it clearly back then.
She had demon wings on her back!
Momo Ayase.
She's definitely a demon!
But since I suddenly became
able to see things like that,
then I must be a chosen individual!
I had hunches that I was.
I mean, I'm all too pretty!
As proof, this fell down from the sky.
A golden ball!
This is telling me to save this world
from evil demons!
I get it! I'll do it!
I mean, after all, I am a pretty girl!
Ouch!
EPISODE 6
A DANGEROUS WOMAN ARRIVES
Ow! So annoying!
What is this?
A marble?
Huh?
Aira!
I brought that thing you wanted.
I only borrowed it, so be careful.
I finally have all the equipment I need.
HOLY BLESSINGS
AND BANISHMENT PRAYERS
Doesn't this smell oily?
Is this cross genuine?
How should I know?
Hey, are you really doing this?
Of course I am!
I have been chosen
because I'm just too beautiful.
I must save the world!
I'll believe you because I'm your friend,
but Aira, you've been weird lately.
What you're trying to do now
is kinda strange, too.
Hold on a second! What is that!?
There's a woman in a red dress!
Sorry. We don't see it at all.
It can't be! That must be her familiar!
Momo Ayase is trying to spy on us!
Both of you, get low!
Her familiar will find us!
Shiratori, what are you doing?
It's a bit hot today,
so I was feeling how cold the wall is.
Shiratori, you're such a ditz.
Hey, I am not!
But people often say that I am.
So pesky.
WE'RE GONNA DO IT AFTER SCHOOL.
YOU CAN'T TELL ANYONE ABOUT IT!
You really are a ditz.
- Oh no, you're getting Aira in trouble!
- Right? Yeah, no doubt.
Hey.
Yes?
I'm telling you to look at me!
I'm watching over Turbo Granny
so she doesn't run off somewhere!
You won't be able to stop me.
Wait, why is Granny at school!?
Huh? Why do I have to take orders
from ya?
Cuz you lost against me.
Bring it on, punk! I'll take you on!
- Yeah! Come at me!
- I'll get you!
Anyway, Turbo Granny said
she found a strange woman.
Why don't we talk about that?
That's right. Don't think I was just
simply strolling around the school.
I was looking for them golden balls, too.
Huh? Why would the golden balls
be at school, idiot?
All right, you're dead meat.
Goodbye to you!
It's worth a search, I think.
I didn't think about it, but there's a possibility
that a human, and not a yokai, picked them up.
It looks like a pretty ball made of gold.
It wouldn't be a surprise
if anyone picked it up.
However, if a human picked it up,
it might awaken their spiritual powers
and depending on the person,
allow them to see spirits.
The fact they can see spirits means
the spirits can see them, too.
There's the danger
that they might get attacked.
That's terrible.
You should've said so earlier!
Who is this strange woman?
I don't know her name.
I'll go introduce her to you after school.
Momo Ayase!
Just how much power does she have?
Can I defeat her with just the cross
and the holy book they got for me?
Besides, she has a familiar.
Can I take both of them on at once?
She's getting closer!
The woman in the red dress!
Okarun!
All right, time to go look!
Where's Granny?
She's in my backpack.
Miss Momo Ayase.
I need to talk to you. Alone.
Huh? What? I'm busy right now.
It'll be over quickly, so please.
This girl is the one
who I dropped the washtub onto.
Has she caught onto something?
It might get annoying later,
so I guess I'll go.
Okarun, go ahead and start looking.
I'll join you later!
What?
Okay.
Oh, brother. I'm not sure
if I can look for it alone.
It's her.
Huh?
You brought me all the way here.
What'd you wanna talk about?
Die, demon!
It stinks! It smells oily! What is it?
O demon, return to the world
you belong in!
Hold her legs!
Make sure she doesn't move!
You idiots!
There they are! The demon wings!
The cross isn't working!
If that's the case...
If I use the golden ball
I received from the heavens...
That's...
So you picked up the ball?
You know about this ball?
I won't give this ball to you!
This is a sacred ball
that I was given to save the world with!
No way! That's Okarun's family jewels!
Give it back, moron!
You're the worst!
How dare you say that
to the sacred ball! How vulgar!
Damn you!
Ouch! Are you
a complete idiot?
Don't revere someone else's
nutsack so much!
Miss Ayase! I found it!
Okarun! You're a serious lifesaver!
She's got your ball!
She's the strange woman!
He's on her side?
That's not true!
She's not the strange woman!
She's the one who's being targeted
by the strange woman.
I finally have you now, Aira.
I've been waiting all this time
until you became able to see me.
Mommy!
Here's Mommy!
The familiar!
Okarun! Do it!
Okay!
What a surprise!
Are you after my little Aira?
You were a demon, too?
Man, I hate this...
I wanna go home.
I feel so withered...
I won't let you have Aira!
Okarun!
Don't you just be eating him!
Come on!
Damn it!
My hands are tied
so I can't control it the way I want!
We finally meet, Aira.
I waited for over ten years
for you to look at me, Aira.
Hey, you! You're not
Momo Ayase's familiar?
Don't "Hey you" me, moron!
I am your Mommy!
Just how much do you think
that I've loved you?
You called me Mommy back then!
I was so happy about that.
It was the first time
you said anything like that.
Please call me that one more time.
Now, call me Mommy!
Hey, damn old hag.
Give Okarun back.
I thought assaulting humans
was against the rules!
Each and every one of you...
I am in the middle
of an emotional reunion here.
Hold it, Momo Ayase!
What in the world is this thing?
Is it possible that you're enemies
with this demon?
If so, why don't we cooperate
and defeat this demon together?
What the hell are you talking about?
Whew, that was close.
I was about to be that thing's side dish.
Turbo Granny!
That's Acrobatic Silky.
Wait, that's Muko's phone!
You pilfered it to do internet searches?
Let's see. A red dress, acrobatic movements,
and silky hair.
You're a yokai yourself,
but you don't know anything about her?
I don't care about rookie nobodies.
I am a chosen one!
Because I'm too pretty!
I defeat monsters like you!
Aira-chan, what did you just say?
I'm going to defeat monsters like you,
and uphold world peace!
Knock it off! Why are you
chomping 'em all down?
It's all your fault!
You tempted Aira
into becoming a delinquent!
She called me a monster!
She would never have said that before!
Granny, hurry up and get this zip tie off!
Oh, that's impossible.
Come on, cooperate a little bit!
She just ate Okarun!
This'll be bad for me to face alone!
You guys were the ones
who took my power from me.
I can't do anything for ya.
No way!
First, how about you apologize!
It's all your fault, after all!
Now, say it!
Piece of crap.
Girgle.
My acrobatics are like a violent storm!
Ensnaring anything and everything,
then swing them away!
Here!
Oh, you're such a hopeless child.
This is Aira's special privilege, but if you want
to say it that badly, you may.
Try saying "Mommy" right now.
I'll forgive you if you do.
Come on!
I can't hear you.
You have to say it properly.
Ready? "M-O-M-M-Y."
I told you to say it, damn brat!
Say, "Mommy"!
You...
Piece of crap.
Where is my baby?
Come on now, you got gobbled up.
Hey, nobody.
I'm still willing to forgive you,
so return the brats you swallowed.
What are you?
Can you not speak to me right now?
Why don't you speak politely, punk!
I am your elder by far.
Sounds like you've got a death wish.
A beckoning cat supposedly has the ability
to beckon over some good fortune.
You ate some hair when you ate Momo.
So hot!
What is this!? My hair is burning!
It's burning inside my body, too!
What did you do to me,
you foul feline?
That cross that the girl
was holding was a lighter.
Momo took that lighter
and lit your hair on fire.
There's nothing combustible
inside your body.
But you coincidentally ate your own hair.
Such fortuity becomes inevitability
because I'm here.
So hot!
Miss Ayase, that's being too reckless!
Huh? Okarun, you were the first to be eaten!
Don't preach to me!
Rescue successful!
Time for the counterattack, damn it!
I will uphold peace in this world!
EPISODE 7
TO A KINDER WORLD
Next episode, "To a Kinder World"